const BadBunnyQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What is Bad Bunny's real name?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Ricardo Martin',
            b: 'Benito Antonio Martínez Ocasio',
            c: 'Luis Fonsi',
            d: 'Rafael Pérez'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these songs is a hit single by Bad Bunny?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Despacito',
            b: 'Dákiti',
            c: 'Vivir Mi Vida',
            d: 'El Perdón'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "In which year did Bad Bunny release his debut album 'X 100pre'?",
        answers: {
            a: '2018',
            b: '2017',
            c: '2019',
            d: '2020'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: "Bad Bunny is known for being a pioneer in which music genre?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Reggaeton',
            b: 'Latin Trap',
            c: 'Salsa',
            d: 'Bachata'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "Which popular song did Bad Bunny collaborate on with Cardi B and J Balvin?",
        answers: {
            a: 'I Like It',
            b: 'MIA',
            c: 'Callaíta',
            d: 'Tusa'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Bad Bunny's third studio album, released in 2020?",
        answers: {
            a: 'YHLQMDLG',
            b: 'El Último Tour Del Mundo',
            c: 'X 100pre',
            d: 'Oasis'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "Bad Bunny made his acting debut in which season of 'Narcos: Mexico'?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Season 2',
            b: 'Season 3',
            c: 'Season 4',
            d: 'Season 1'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "Which 2022 sports event did Bad Bunny perform at?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Super Bowl Halftime Show',
            b: 'NBA All-Star Game',
            c: 'FIFA World Cup Opening Ceremony',
            d: 'Olympic Games Opening Ceremony'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the title of Bad Bunny's collaboration with Drake?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Te Boté',
            b: 'MIA',
            c: 'La Canción',
            d: 'Vete'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "In addition to his music career, Bad Bunny has also been involved in which sport?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Basketball',
            b: 'Soccer',
            c: 'Wrestling',
            d: 'Boxing'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    }
];